<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Containerd on Welcome to my site</title>
    <link>/tags/containerd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Containerd on Welcome to my site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/containerd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Free Functions as a service</title>
      <link>/posts/free-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/free-functions/</guid>
      <description>Intro Five minutes (almost!) to always free functions as a service courtesy of Oracle Cloud The full source code for this project is here.
Why do this? All the major cloud providers offer some level of free service, however Oracle cloud is the only one offering this much compute free forever.
Yeah but why Oracle? Okay you got me. I got sucked into their free tier. Plus I like the way they describe instances sizes/flavours as shapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenFAAS with TLS via Faasd and Terraform on Openstack</title>
      <link>/posts/openfaas-openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/openfaas-openstack/</guid>
      <description>Intro OpenFAAS is a serverless tool. One of the things I like most about it - it&amp;rsquo;s pretty agnostic. You can bring your own infra or orchestrator and roll with Dockerfiles (as long as they conform to the OpenFaas serverless workload definition). No vendor lock in!
Their tagline: OpenFaaS® makes it simple to deploy both functions and existing code to Kubernetes
While OpenFaas is mainly used with k8s, there are other providers available too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenFAAS via Containerd on a Raspberry PI 4</title>
      <link>/posts/pi4-containerd-openfaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pi4-containerd-openfaas/</guid>
      <description>Intro OpenFAAS is a serverless tool. One of the things I like most about it - it&amp;rsquo;s pretty agnostic. You can bring your own infra or orchestrator and roll with Dockerfiles. No vendor lock in!
Their tagline: OpenFaaS® makes it simple to deploy both functions and existing code to Kubernetes
While it is mainly used with k8s, there are also providers for other orchestrators, such as Hashicorp&amp;rsquo;s Nomad. Today I&amp;rsquo;ll be trying out a new provider for Containerd on my Raspberry Pi 4b.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
